Say what you want to say to me now. I
want to wake up with you in the morning.
>> I always feel so gay when I'm around
you, Astro.
>> You You what?
>> You know I I always feel gay when I'm
around you, too. Maybe we can keep this
gayness going. I can pick you up
tomorrow at 8:00 and we can go to the
roller skating rink and share a Pepsi
and some mozzarella sticks if you want.
I like the sound of that. It'll be a
date.
>> I'd better scuaddle home to feed Pebble.
It's Tuesday, which means he gets a can
of Spaghettiios.
>> These were just on Danny's dirty and
stinky feet. I shouldn't. Danny is a
dear friend.
Oh my freaking god.
>> Coup.
>> Dandy, how are you doing?
>> Oh yeah, I forgot you and Scraps don't
got a house since I said I would get you
to one when you first moved in, but I
never really got around to doing it cuz
I didn't really care.
>> Do you have any spare change or food
that we could borrow? My sister hasn't
been able to eat in two whole days.
Anything will help.
Oh, to be a goober beneath my dirty and
stinky feet. I've got a dollar. Do you
want it?
>> I I do. I want it. You're cute. How bad
do you want it? Will you beg for it?
>> Please don't make me do that. I can't do
it again.
Why? I want it. I need it so bad. Dandy,
I'll do anything to help my sister.
>> Anything. Huh?
>> What's going on over there? Golly, it's
the neighborhood watch. If Roger asks I
was never here, you got that goober.
>> Oh, morning Astro. What do you want?
>> I'm here to pick you up for our first
official date as boyfriends.
>> Boyfriends? Since when did we become
each other's boyfriends? Boys can't be
together. That's weird and gross.
>> You said that you feel gay when you're
around me, so I just thought
>> I meant gay as in happy, you idiot. The
original definition for gay in the
dictionary is literally to be carefree
and joyful. It was a wonderful word
before the gays took it for themselves.
You know, the Bible says that it's a sin
for two boys to be each other's
boyfriends, right?
>> Oh, haha. Yeah, of course I knew that. I
just came here to mess with you. Haha,
surprise.
>> Can you get off my porch?
>> Oh, um, yeah. Sorry. Are we still going
out for some Pepsi and mozzarella
sticks, though?
Good morning, Cosmo. Good morning,
Sprout.
Do you remember what day it is? It's
Tuesday. So, you're going on one of
those neighborhood watch patrols with
Roger, right? I promised Roger I would
bring some freshly baked cookies to the
meeting, and I decided you're going to
help me bake them.
That must be Astro and Goob. They wanted
to come over and help us bake. Astro,
why the long-faced sugar tits?
>> I embarrassed myself in front of Dandy.
Cosmo, why the hell is the corner of V's
head all screwed up? That one was the
last one I did. I made it with what
little was left of the dough because I
didn't want it to go to waste sprout.
You can't just punch me in the neck like
that. That's how you paralyze someone. I
am not going to show up to the
neighborhood watch meeting with halfass
cookies. Do you want to make me look
like a loser in front of Roger? It's
just the two of you. Why do you even
need 60 cookies anyway? Stop hitting me
in front of our friends. They're my
friends, not yours. Nobody ever comes
over to hang out with you, Cosmo. We
both know that to be true, but you don't
have to say it. You don't talk back to
me, [__] I own you. I'm the one paying
54% of the rent each month. You're only
paying 46%. That's practically nothing.
Apologize. Sorry. Say it louder, [__]
Apologize to Astro. I said I'm sorry.
Now go in the bedroom and put on that
gay fem twink outfit and come back and
say sorry again like a good [__] Not
until you send Astro and Goob home. Are
you squaring up on me? How many times do
I got to tell you not to do that? Go.
Gay punch. Gay punch. Gay punch. Secret
strawberry swing attack.
You get back here.
>> I'm sorry. Sprout.
>> Short shorts. Excellent choice. Sprout.
You forgot the collar. How am I supposed
to let Astro and Goo take turns walking
you around for the next half hour?
>> Sprout, we don't really want to do that.
Astro, shut up. Don't ruin this for us.
>> You're right, Sprout. I'll I'll go get
the collar right now.
Hey, hands off the merchandise, pal.
>> What? It wasn't me.
Where the hell did you go? You dweeb.
>> Cosmo, what do you want,
Dandy? You've got to let me inside. Why
do you keep looking over your shoulder?
Who's chasing you? It's Sprout. He's
been hitting me all morning. I just
don't know what to do, Dandy. It's like
this between us every day. Now listen,
Cosmo, what you go through is
unfortunately just the norm for gay
couples. It's why I don't partake in
such urges. You get urges? Most tunes
do. Dandy are Are you gay? No, I'm
homophobic. Believe me, I would like
nothing more than to ravage Astro's
mind, body, and soul and claim him for
myself. That's sounding kind of gay to
me, dog. Put down Pebble. He has done
nothing to you. Open up, Dork. I know
Cosmo is in there. He is not. Go away. I
don't like yelling. Come to the door so
we can talk face to face.
You need to stop or I'm calling the
cops.
>> Jesus Christ, you kicked me right in my
eyeball.
>> It's your own fault for looking out the
mail slot and being such an easy target.
Don't think I can't see your big head,
Cosmo. Coward
>> Sprout, this is bananas. You have got to
stop this. Yo, Dandicus, don't use my
government given name. If you're going
to hold my boy hostage, then you best be
ready to say bye-bye to your boy Astro
out here. Is that a threat?
Astro, no. Can't you just go away?
You're scaring me. I don't like fighting
with you like this. Yeah, don't you have
somewhere to be? Like your stupid
neighborhood watch meeting? Actually,
Dandy, don't think I didn't see your
name on the signup sheet outside Roger's
front door. I know you're part of the
neighborhood watch now, too. So, why
don't you step outside and we can head
to Roger's place together. Or are you
scared that I'm going to beat you up?
Um, duh. That's enough, Sprout. Please,
just stop it. Go away. Stop talking for
a bit and maybe he'll leave. Cosmo
Dandy, come on. Just do as I say. God
dang it. You know I don't got any other
friends.
Okay, he's gone.
>> Hey, Roger. Nice booty cheeks you got
there.
>> Hey, Roger. Do you and your butt I I
mean, do you want to come to my house
and hang out?
>> Good morning, Roger. You have a really
big butt. Want to go to Olive Garden and
share a tray of neverending bread
sticks?
>> I do not. Good day.
>> Ah, come on. You must be so tired after
carrying that thing around all day. Why
not relax by sitting it down next to me?
>> I said no. Good day to you.
Will I ever have friends in my life who
care about me for a reason other than
the fact that I am carrying around a
whole entire bakery? It's just like that
time at the movies last week. Hey, are
you are you all sure nobody wants to sit
down here next to me? It's kind of
lonely having a row all to myself.
>> Oh, no, Roger. We're all good back here
watching your butt. I I mean the movie.
Thanks, though.
>> Or that time at the park, which was also
last week.
>> Dandy, it's my turn to push Roger. We
agreed to switch off every 10 minutes.
No. Goob went 3 minutes overtime, which
mean I get 3 minutes overtime, too. How
about I push one of you for a change?
>> You stay out of this, Roger. This isn't
about you. Yeah, Roger, shut up.
>> Oh, Dandy, welcome. It is a pleasure to
finally have the mayor of Garden View
join the neighborhood watch.
>> Hey, what can I say, Roger? I'm curious
to see how you've been keeping my
neighborhood safe without my overbearing
eye over your head. I hear it's just you
and Sprout. What's that about? Are you
two like homosexuals together or
something? Ah, Sprout. You see, it
wasn't always this way. There was once a
time when just about every resident of
Garden View was a member of the
neighborhood watch program. Did
everybody remember to bring their
flashlights and extra batteries? One day
during a patrol, I told the group to
watch my six. But what they must have
heard instead was, "Watch my big bouncy
butt cheeks." Sprout was the only tune
who kept his eyes on the neighborhood
streets instead of the goods. He walked
proudly by my side and was the only one
able to control his lustful desires
around me. There were on record nine
breakins that night, and while everyone
else was distracted by my cheeks, Sprout
actually did his damn job and prevented
two of them. If he hadn't, the number of
break-ins would have been in the double
digits, which would have been crazy as
hell. I had to kick all of my friends
out of the program shortly after that.
The only one who stayed was Sprout.
>> Sup, Roger. Sup, Tweeb. I baked cookies
for us. Where should I put them?
>> The usual spot in the kitchen is fine.
>> So, what did you bring, Dandy?
I just stopped by the vending machine
outside my house and got each of us a
packet of famous Amos cookies. Are you
dead ass? I poured sweat over an oven to
bring freshly baked cookies, and you
can't even do the bare minimum. Vending
machine cookies are not enough to fuel
us. How much fuel do we need? Aren't we
just going up and down the block? It'll
take like 7 minutes.
>> Pizza. Pizza. Pizza. Pizza. Pizza.
Pizza. Pizza.
>> What is that?
>> That's Goob's AAC machine. It helps for
when he's stmming. He has autism.
>> Your brother was born mentally
handicapped. Ain't that the funniest
thing in the world?
>> Leave Goob alone, Shrimpo.
>> Hey, Goob. Since you have the mentality
of a three-year-old, does that mean
you'll never meaningfully be able to
consent to
>> It's okay, Goob. Calm down. Glisten, can
you tell Shrimpo to leave,
>> girl? Aha. Now, why should I do that?
>> Because you're the host of this outing.
You're the one paying for everybody's
dinner. You are the only one with the
power to threaten him to leave.
>> Scraps, baby girl. Every tune has the
rights to their beliefs. If your ugly
autistic brother didn't want to, you
know, be bullied, then he he shouldn't
have, you know, been born wrong, like
why did you let him bring his AAC unit?
You knew it was going to be embarrassing
after that. Cosmo, are you still sad
about Sprout beating you like a [__]
>> What do you think? Sprout was the
bestest friend and finest piece of ass
this Swiss roll has ever had, and now he
hates me.
>> Maybe you could try texting him. If you
want, we could help figure out what to
say.
>> Why do you keep stopping? Will you stay
out of my business, tweeb? Cosmo keeps
texting me at this hour. Is your
emotional support fruitcake baker boy
toy twink looking for his nightly booty
call? Stop being homophobic. Pick up the
pace. I need to go home and poopy in my
toilet.
What do you want? I'm really sorry about
this morning. Please don't be mad at me.
Where are you right now?
Nowhere.
I'm at Domino's Pizza. Why?
If you're really sorry, you would send
me an armpit pick
now.
I'm hanging up. Hanging.
Wait, I'll send it.
>> Are you sending it or not? Okay, cuz
I'll turn my phone off if you're not
serious.
What did he say?
>> I have to go to the bathroom real quick.
Is Tis God.
What?
It's fine.
I stopped to text you. I have to catch
up with Roger. K. Learn to take better
pit pics. I'm turning my phone off, so
don't text me again. Love you.
All right.
How did it go?
>> It went great. Yeah, great.
>> Can you send me the armpit picture? I
want to look at it. I really like that
kind of stuff.
>> Sprout, we've got a problem. It's goo
and scraps. They haven't eaten all day
again.
>> Not those panhandling losers again. I
told you two last night to stop dirtying
up my streets. Get lost. Dandy, what are
you doing? Have you been feeding these
two?
>> We do what we can.
>> It's because of you two then that they
are out here. If you keep giving them
free [__] they are never going to get
off of their asses to work. Nobody wants
to work these days.
>> We do it because you won't give them a
house. Please, we're so hungry.
>> Glisten invited us to Domino's Pizza.
>> It was going to be our first meal in
weeks. But before the pizza was served,
Goob and Cosmo got into a fight because
Cozmo wouldn't give Goobb a picture of
his armpit. So Goob lifted Cosmo's arm
and took a picture of his armpit by
force. And so security threw Goo out.
And because I was standing in the
doorway of Domino's, Goob bumped into me
and I fell out of the building, too.
Dandy, stop.
You know, Roger, I've really been
considering joining the neighborhood
watch.
>> Goo, my boy. I'll have you know, you
wouldn't be disappointed with these two
around.
>> What's going on out here? It's the
middle of the night. Shouldn't you all
be in bed? Dandy took offense to Sprout
and I wanting to give these homeless
tunes food.
>> Goob, you and your sister are living on
the streets.
>> It's It's not something I like to talk
about openly.
>> You're too sexy to be homeless. This is
my lunch I prepared for work tomorrow.
You can have it.
>> Are you sure? This is what I have left
over from dinner. You can have this
also.
>> And mine too, [__]
>> No. Stop. This town is not one built on
kindness. It is one built on capitalism.
And I am at the top.
>> And here you can have mine.
>> Halfeaten PB&J's.
Thanks. Oh no. Dandy is coming back
over.
>> Forgive me, Dandy. But you leave me no
choice. Those who join the neighborhood
watch program take an oath upon their
admission that they shall never harm a
fellow resident. You have become the
very thing you swore to stand against.
Die. Damn you. Die. Die. Die.
>> I'll live you. Roger. I'll live you.
>> You did it. Roger.
>> You saved their cardboard box. Roger.
>> Do you hear that? Roger. They are all
cheering for you.
>> No, they aren't. They are all cheering
for my butt like always.
>> No, Roger. Don't you see? You're the one
who put your pooper to work. Your butt
cheeks may make up 95% of your total
body weight, but it's still only a part
of you.
>> You know what? Yeah, you're right. I'm
carrying the largest bakery in Garden
View on my backside. That is something I
should be proud of. No one else can say
that.
>> Okay.
See, this is why everybody in all of
Garden View hates you and why we trash
talk you behind your back. You have the
most god-awful attitude ever. And you
smell bad. What? Tunes don't trash talk
me. I'm beloved by everybody. You think
Goob and Scraps love you after the stunt
you pulled tonight? Those two don't need
to love me as long as they fear me.
Okay, which is it then? Are you loved or
feared? You can't have both. The only
cold hard truth is Dandy is that we all
hate you.
I I didn't mean it like that.
>> Hey, I just wanted to say I'm sorry,
dork. It's not like you were lying back
there. I know you're right.
>> What I said might have some truth do it
about tounes talking behind your back.
But if it makes you feel any better, I
never participated in the trash talking.
Yeah, right. Why wouldn't you?
>> Oh, come on, Dandy. If I have a problem
with you, I don't need to go to others
about it. I'll just say it to your face.
You know me. We're rivals like that.
>> Hey, have you guys noticed how fat
Dandy's been getting recently?
>> Yeah. I ordered six big buckets of
cheesy balls off of walmart.com and it
never came. I found out last week that
Dandy had forwarded it back to his own
house so that he could eat all six
buckets in like 4 minutes. They're
called cheese balls blot, not cheesy
balls. Anyway, he's already so short
that soon he's going to be wider than he
is tall. Haha.
>> Hey, lay off him, you guys. It's not
right to talk about someone behind their
back like that. How would you feel if he
was doing that to you,
Dandy?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have done that. I
mean, I just fell forward. I'm not gay.
>> No, I I just I get it, girl. I fell
forward, too. It was an accident.
>> Do you have anything else you want to
say to me? If not, I'm fine now with
being alone.
Actually, I think there's someone else
here who wants to talk to you.
>> Hey, Dandy. I know you didn't want to go
on that date we talked about, but I went
to the Dollar Tree and picked up some
Pepsi and frozen mozzarella sticks. We
can't heat them up since we're outside,
but I bought these 7 hours ago, so they
are soggy enough that we can eat them
the way they are now. I'll leave you two
fart boxes alone, then.
How much of that did you see?
>> Enough to say that. Maybe I wish I
hadn't.
>> Do you maybe want to go roller skating
tomorrow like we talked about?
>> Oh, I'd like that if you're serious this
time. We don't have to. And it's okay if
you change your mind again,
>> Astro. I want to because I always feel
so gay when I'm around you. You know,
at this rate, little bro, we're going to
have that house right there by tomorrow
morning.
Sprout Cosmo, what are you doing out
here? Goob and Scrabs were kicked out of
Domino's Pizza because of my armpit. So,
I snuck out to bring them a couple of
slices by hiding them in my fem thigh
high socks.
Were you trying to text me? I turned my
phone off so I wouldn't waste the
battery since you said you were turning
yours off, too. Are you done with the
neighborhood watch patrol? Do you want
to walk home together?
Cosmo, your armpit pick was good. like
really really good. Oh, um, thanks. I
could practically smell it through the
screen. It's no wonder why it caused so
much trouble tonight. I'm sorry. What do
you got to be sorry about for hitting
you this morning and chasing you down
the block and hitting you again at Dy's
house? It's okay. I deserved it for
running away. If I ever make you feel
scared of me again, you've got to tell
me. I can't have you feeling ashamed for
who you are like Roger was. And I don't
want to just be a bully like Dandy. Will
you promise to tell me if I'm ever
hurting your feelings? I will, Sprout. I
promise. Now go put on your collar,
[__] A toast to a wonderful night.
>> And most importantly to the fact that I
finally made another friend who cares
about me for more than just my fat
cheeks.
>> You didn't just make another friend
today, Roger. You made a best friend.
May we make many more memories together
now that the three baddest [__] in
Garden View are running the neighborhood
watch. Yeah, very cool. It would
probably ruin the moment right now if I
told him I'm actually leaving the
neighborhood watch program after this
because I don't really care.
>> Hey there kiddos. It's me, Sprout from
Dandy's World. Today I'm going to teach
you all how to do the floss dance so you
can pick up [__] like me. To start,
we're going to put our hands down to the
side. Then we're going to ball our hands
into fists like this. Are you with me?
Are you with me now? Cuz here comes the
part that is really fun. Swing your hips
to one side like this and swing your
arms out in the opposite direction.
Next, you're going to bring both your
arms back, but make sure one of them
goes behind your fat butt and the other
goes in front like this.
Now, bring them back out. Now, instead
of only swinging them halfway, we're
going to swing them in front of us and
to the other side. Watch me closely if
you want to learn how to pick up
[__]
Now, we're going to do what we did
before on this side. Bring them in.
Bring one fist in front and the other
behind your fat butt. Now, if we combine
it all together, we got the floss dance.
Haha. See, you're doing it. You're a
real bad [__] Now, come on. Let's see
how long we can go. The longer you go,
the more [__] you'll pick up in the
schoolyard.
Haha. Yeah. 67. 67. Yeah. Wee! Wee!
Wow.